迈阿密
慢点好吗 迈克?你搞得我不舒服
Hey, slow down, Mike, okay? You're making me sick.
如果不是你害我们迟到 我会慢点的
I would slow down if you hadn't already made us late.
我们没迟到好吗?是你太紧张
We're... We're not late, okay? You're just anxious.
不 我紧张是因为你害我们迟到
No, I'm anxious 'cause you made us late.
我下半生一定不会和你一起这样做
I'm not doin' this with you in the next phase of our lives.
你必须尊重我的时间
You're gon' respect my time.
我的肚子
My stomach. My stomach.
迈克 马上在那家店前停车
Hey, Mike, look, pull over at that store right there.
我需要姜汁汽水
I need a ginger ale.
我们没时间买姜汁汽水 老兄
Look, we don't have no time to get no ginger ale, man.
别这样 迈克 我不舒服
Come on, Mike, I'm sick.
你吓死我了 知道吗?
You're freaking me out, okay?
我觉得我快要吐了
I feel like I'm gonna throw... throw up.
我挑战你 马克斯
I dare you, Marcus.
你有90秒 知道吗?
You got 90 seconds, all right?
只能买姜汁汽水
Ginger ale and nothing else.
我是个成人好吗?
I am a grown-ass man, okay?
对我好点吧
Just be nice.
好吧 85秒
Oh. Okay. 85 seconds.
那些热狗新鲜吗?
Are those dogs fresh?
昨天才摆出来的
I put 'em on yesterday.
给我一个 上面放点佐料和芥末
Well, give me one and put some relish and some mustard on that motherfucker.
拿起来 来 快点
Hook it up. Come on, hurry up.
不 那边那个 对 那个 快点
No, that one right there. Yeah. Yeah, that right there. Hurry up.
该走了
Gotta go, gotta go.
别慢吞吞的
Don't be takin' your time.
对 就这样嘛
Yeah, my man.
打开收银机
Hey, open the register.
不 马上!
No, no, no. Now!
先生 你选错日子了
Sir, today is not the day.
闭嘴!
Shut the fuck up!
看 如果我不在15秒之内上车
Look, if I'm not in that car in 15 seconds,
有个脾气暴躁的男人会进来 我们都完蛋了
there's a very surly man that's comin' in here and we both are fucked.
马克斯 别动
Marcus. Hey, don't fuckin' move.
过去!
The fuck over there!
迈克 我跟这人说了我必须走了
'Ey, Mike, I told this guy I had to go.
柜台上那是彩虹糖吗 马克斯?
Is that Skittles on the counter, Marcus?
他花了很久时间卖我姜汁汽水
Well, he was takin' a long time with the ginger ale.
不对 他进来时就马上拿了姜汁汽水
That is incorrect. He grabbed that ginger ale the second he came in here.
是热狗吗 马克斯?
A hot dog, Marcus?
你根本不该吃那鬼东西
You're not supposed to be eatin' that shit.
这不是我的 迈克 是你的
This is not mine, Mike. Yes, it is.
你别多管闲事
Mind your business with your tattletaling ass.
大家都闭嘴!
Everybody shut the fuck up!
先生 你必须把武器放下
Sir, I'm gonna need you to lower your weapon.
不然你来拿我的武器吧
Come take my weapon, then, motherfucker.
别跟他作对
Don't antagonise him.
马克斯 上车
Marcus, get in the car.
迈克 他拿枪指着我的头
Mike, he has a gun to my head.
你想对付他 还是我?
Wanna deal with him, you wanna deal with me?
抱歉 先生 我必须走了
Sorry, sir, but I gotta go.
你不必向他开枪 迈克
You didn't have to shoot him, Mike.
上车
Get in the car.
打911
Call 911.
你们不是警察?
Aren't you the police?
绝地战警: 生死与共
别人眼里的你
Other people look at you
看到的是量身定制的西装 汽车 手表
and see the tailored suits, the cars, the watches.
我们相识时 那一切都不存在
I met you without any of that.
一丝不挂 基本上是赤身裸体
Stripped, basically naked...
那是90%我嫁给你的原因
which is 90% of why I'm marrying you.
我在你最低谷时遇见了你
I met you at your lowest.
你中了枪
You'd been shot.
但你内心的火
But there was a fire in you that was...
是非凡的
...extraordinary.
我发誓要用余生来煽动那股火焰
And I vow to spend the rest of my life fanning that flame.
现在我宣布
I now pronounce you...
你们结为夫妻
husband and wife.
你可以吻新娘
You may kiss the bride.
太好了!
Yes!
我好喜欢
I love it.
他在中枪后与治疗师结婚是有道理的
You know, it kinda makes sense that he married his therapist after he got shot.
我喜欢他一点 心理健康非常重要
I love that for him. Mental health is super important.
那是他的物理治疗师
Well, it was his physical therapist.
恭喜 迈克 丽塔 谢谢你
Congratulations, Michael. Rita. Thank you, thank you.
市长先生
Mr Mayor.
说早了就不灵了 我仍然只是个卑微的美国律师
Oh, not yet. Don't jinx it. I'm still just a lowly US Attorney.
我一直在关注你的工作
I've been watching what you're doin'.
我支持你 谢谢
You got my vote. Thank you.
恭喜你
Congratulations to you.
你们就是金童玉女
I mean, the definition of a power couple right there.
我去帮你拿饮料 好
I'll grab you a drink. Okay.
你想要什么吗?不 不需要 谢谢
Can I get you anything? No, I'm good, thank you.
一直以来 我都以为你至死都是单身汉
And all this time, I thought you were a terminal bachelor.
这一次我自己也始料不及
I... I... I even surprised myself with this one.
我想你一直没遇见对的人
Yeah, I guess you just hadn't met the right one.
那时候我还有待成长
I had some growing up to do.
当时你已经50岁了
You were 50.
好
Okay.
我得为他所说的一切预先道歉
I'm gonna pre-apologise for whatever he says.
迈克
Mike.
不行 你也知道的 马克斯!
No, you know how it is. Don't... Marcus!
马克斯 让我说出来!
Marcus. Come... Let me get it out!
别这样 兄弟
Come on, man.
你经历了那么多 好吧
Everything you have been through, man. Okay.
女巫 巫师
The witch. The Bruja.
妓女
The prostitute.
我妹妹 记得吗?你应该跟我说我妹妹的事 迈克
My sister. 'Member? You coulda told me about my sister, Mike.
你早该告诉我的
You coulda told me that.
如果她对你有感觉 我会拥抱你的
I would've embraced you, if that's who she was feeling.
我爱你 迈克 无庸置疑
I love you, Mike. No doubt.
如果警监还活着 他一定想亲眼目睹这一幕
You know, Cap would've loved to have been here to see this.
但你知道吗?
But you know what?
我们找到了他的女儿朱迪和孙女凯莉
We got his daughter, Judy, and his granddaughter, Callie.
她有话想说
She wants to say something.
我爷爷很爱大家
My grandad loved you guys.
如果他在这里 他会说不要把这件事搞砸
And if he were here, he would have told you not to F this up.
他会这么说的
That's what he would've said.
是啊 他会说"别搞砸了"
Yeah, he woulda said "Don't fuck it up."
没错
Exactly.
抱歉我说脏话了
Oh, excuse me.
嘿
'Ey.
迈克 我们成为拍档一段时间了
Mike, you been my partner a long time.
是 先生
Yes, sir.
现在他将成为你的伴侣 克莉斯丁
Now he's gonna be your partner, Christine.
祝贺迈克和克莉斯丁劳瑞
To Mike and Christine Lowrey.
一辈子!一辈子!
For life! For life!
加油 马克斯!
Go Marcus! Go Marcus! Go Marcus! Go Marcus!
糟了
Oh, shit.
发生什么事?
What happened? What happened?
马克斯!
Marcus. Marcus!
这里的地址是什么?
What's the address?
让我进去 退后
Let me in, let me in, let me in. Back up.
我是丽塔塞卡达警监 有一名警官心脏骤停
This is Captain Rita Secada. I have an officer in cardiac arrest.
加油
Come on, man.
你的死期还没到
It's not your time.
马克斯!
Marcus!
马克!
Marc-Marc--!
这家伙
This guy.
哥们
Hey, buddy.
你在干什么?
What you doing?
我一生都在害怕之中 迈克
I spent my whole life being scared, Mike.
我浪费了太多时间
I wasted so much time.
请你从边缘退后一点
Why... Why... Why don't you...Why don't you just step back from the edge a little bit, please.
现在是哪一年?
What year is it?
是星期二
It's Tuesday.
你扭着屁股昏倒的同一年
Same year your ass was wobbling in.
哇 感觉已经有五年了
Oh, wow. Felt like it was five years.
我处于海洋的底部
I was in the basement of the ocean.
我所有的烦恼都消失了
All my bullshit was gone.
唯有自由
Just freedom.
还有完全充满爱 迈克
And full body love, Mike. Full body love.
好
Okay.
不如你
Why... Why... Why don't you...
以爱让你全身从边缘回来好吗?
...love your full body back from the ledge, please?
没什么好怕的
Nothing to be scared of.
我的时间还没到 宝贝
It's not my time, baby. It's not my time.
伯内特先生!
Mr Burnett!
我看着他
Hey, I got him.
他只是
He's just...
我不知道他到底在干嘛
I don't know what the fuck he's doing.
但我看着他了 我们没事
But I got it. I got him. We're good. We are good.
我们很好!
We are great! 'Ey...
迈阿密!
Miami!
305一辈子!
305 for life!
唰唰!
Kakow!
停 你那东西会闪瞎别人的眼睛
All right. Just stop. You gon' put somebody's eye out with that thing, man.
我在唤醒我的原始能量 迈克
I'm bringing the thunder, Mike. I get it.
唤醒能量
Bringing the thunder.
好 就是这样
All right. There you go.
来抱抱
Oh, man. Bring it in.
我以为我已经失去你了 兄弟
Thought I lost you, brother.
你的人生少不了我
Couldn't lose me if you tried.
你知道你的屁股露出了吧?
You know your ass is out, right?
大家的屁股都露出来了 迈克
Everybody's ass is out, Mike.
嘿
Hey.
一场暴风雨要来了
There's a storm coming.
不 不是那种暴风雨
No. Not that kind of storm.
你会经受考验
You're gonna be tested.
事情会变得糟糕
Things are gonna get bad,
你将不得不做出一个非常艰难的选择
and you're gonna have to make a really hard choice.
你只需记住 你很厉害
Just know you're good.
这是我的私人时间 麦格拉斯先生
This is my private time, Mr McGrath.
请问有什么能帮到你的吗?
How may I help you?
我要你转一些钱 你的钱?
I need you to move some money. Your money?
其实是你老板的 我要贩毒集团现金
Your boss's, actually. I need it to be cartel cash.
不到两千万
Just under 20 million.
回溯那账户从2004年到2020年1月的
Backdated series of transfers beginning 2004, ending January 2020...
一系列
into...
转账
...that account.
以已故康拉德霍华德警监的名义
In the name of the late Captain Conrad Howard.
我有负责物流的人
I have people who can handle logistics.
我只需要你的登录信息
I really just need your log-in credentials.
我为什么要给你这些?
And why would I give you those?
天啊!
Oh, my God!
过来 亲爱的
Come here, darling.
来
Come on.
过来
Come here.
面部识别
手机无法转账
You can't transfer funds from a phone.
亲爱的 怎么了?
Hey, honey, what's going on?
她们互相认识吗?
Do they know each other?
亲爱的 谁在你身边?
Honey, who's there with you?
好!亲爱的?
All right, all right! Honey--
转账开始了
Here we go.
资金转移
转至:康拉德霍华德
他们会为此杀了你
They'll kill you for this.
他们不会知道事情的经过
They're not even gonna know this happened.
你的女友听见你和你太太的电话
Your girlfriend heard you on the phone with your wife
发现你根本没打算和她离婚
and realised you were never gonna divorce her.
她一怒之下开枪射杀了你
And in a fit of passion, she shot you.
你的保镖试图介入 但已经来不及了
Your bodyguard tried to step in, but he was too late.
当她意识到她那恐怖的行为
And realising the horror of her actions...
她自杀了
she took her own life.
不要!
No!
亲爱的 你在干什么?
Honey, what are you doing?
两星期前你才心脏病发作 没错
You had a heart attack two weeks ago. Exactly.
他们称其为寡妇制造者是有原因的 你该留在医院 宝贝
They call it a widow-maker for a reason. You need to be in the hospital, baby.
我尝试说过他了
Hey, I tried to told his ass, T.
显然 他已经是成年人了 他获准自行出院
Apparently, he's an adult. He was allowed to sign hisself out.
宝贝 别这样 我一刻也无法忍受离开你
Hey, babe. Look, come on. I couldn't take one more second away from you.
我体内的支架让我血脉喷张
All these stents in me got my blood flowing.
我在回家途中 好吧
I'm on D way. All right, now.
拜托 那是我的电话
Ey. Ey. Come on, man. That's my phone.
我爱你 马克斯 我们10分钟后到
I love you, Marcus. We'll be there in 10.
好的 宝贝 爱你
All right, babe. All right. Love you.
嘿 迈克
Hey, Mike.
我没打算告诉你
I wasn't even gonna tell you this...
但我们不是第一次了
but this ain't the first time we done this.
我们时常同车 你是什么意思?
We ride together all the time, what you mean?
不 我是说我们的灵魂
No, I'm talking about our souls.
我们曾一起同车 但我看到了全部 迈克
You know, we've ridden together, but I saw it all, Mike.
我们注定携手同行 已经做了好几辈子的生死搭档
We're bound. And we have been for lifetimes.
我们并不总是叫迈克和马克斯 但我们的灵魂不曾改变
We haven't always been Mike and Marcus, but we've always been us.
你在说什么?
What you talking 'bout?
我们是灵魂伴侣
We're soulmates.
是 是的
Yup. Yeah.
不
Naw.
我认为的灵魂伴侣看起来有点不同
Yeah, I kind of... I saw my soulmate looking a little different than that.
迈克 你被困在肉体里
See... See, Mike, you stuck in the physical.
灵魂没有鸡鸡
Souls don't have dicks.
我蛮肯定我的灵魂有鸡鸡 马克斯
I'm pretty sure my soul has a dick, Marcus.
看吧?就是这些废话 所以我们才被困住
See? That's that shit right there. That's why we're stuck.
我本来也没打算告诉你这个
You know, I wasn't gonna tell you this shit either,
但我的灵魂比你的先进多了
but my soul is more advanced than your soul.
我不是说你的灵魂很笨
It's not that your soul is stupid.
知道吗?
You know?
只是你比较像是婴儿灵魂 知道吗?
It's just that you're more like a baby soul. You know?
而我比较像是母亲的灵魂
And I'm more like a mother soul.
我只想给你喂奶
And I just gotta suckle ya.
知道吗?让你吸奶
You know? Put you on that titty.
知道吗?
You know?
你觉得你的大脑缺氧多久了?
Hey. How long you think your brain went without oxygen?
爸爸!爸爸回来了
Daddy! Daddy's home.
宝贝!宝贝 你回来了 我的家人呢?我的家庭
Baby! Oh, baby, you're back. Where my family? My family.
嗨 宝贝
Hey, baby.
小马克斯!
Little Marcus!
跟奶奶和爷爷说嗨
Say hi to Pop-pop. Say hi to Grandad.
我非常想念!你看你 女人
I missed you so-Look at you, woman.
不 别这样 看着我 宝贝
No, come on, look at me, baby.
我们得让他们冷静下来
We're gonna have to hose them down.
好 我们知道了
All right. All right, we get it. We get it.
放点冰在你的内裤什么的
Put some ice in your drawers or somethin'.
真好笑
That's funny.
你感觉好吗 马克斯?
Are you feeling good, Marcus?
我一生中从未感觉如此好过
I never felt better in my life.
马克斯 我太想你了 亲爱的 但你必须休息
Oh, Marcus, I missed you so much, honey, but you need to get some rest.
不 宝贝 我需要你
Oh, no, baby, I need you.
让我去补充一些电解质 好的 宝贝 给我一个吻
Just let me get some electrolytes. Okay, baby. Give me a kiss.
我爸爸怎么了?
So, what's going on with my dad?
他赤裸地站在屋顶上
Well, he was on the roof naked...
他还说他去了海床
and he said he had been at the basement of the ocean.
"神奇鹰嘴豆"?
"Amazing Chickpeas"?
还有 他说我有个很笨的婴孩灵魂
Oh, and he said I have a stupid baby soul
也没有鸡鸡
with no penis.
你们必须和他谈谈
嘿 雷吉 是 长官
Hey, Reggie. Yes, sir.
你吃了我的零食?没有 长官
Did you eat my snacks? No, sir.
我正期待着我的零食 雷吉
I was looking forward to my snacks, Reggie.
亲爱的
Honey.
你知道吗?你该去找份工作
You know what? You need to get a job.
我是一名美国海军陆战队员 长官
I'm a US Marine, sir.
那么你该被调派出去
Well, then you need to deploy.
我们刚从也门回来
You know, we just got back from Yemen.
谢谢你为国效力
Thank you for your service.
你以为我死了 对吗?死了?
You thought I was dead, didn't you? Dead?
有一件事你不知道 雷吉
One thing you don't know, Reggie.
我在这安了一台监控 没错
I got a camera up in here. Yeah.
特丽莎!
Theresa!
是医生吩咐的 马克斯 你要严格节食 无盐 无糖 无脂肪
It's the doctor's orders, Marcus. You're on a strict diet. No salt, no sugar, no fats.
不能有压力 吵闹声 消耗体力
No stress, no loud noises, no physical exertion.
你随便坐下就是了
Just sit your ass down somewhere, man.
告诉他 迈克
Tell him, Mike.
还有 亲爱的 我和你一起做 现在我们是素食者
And, honey, I'm doing it with you. We're now vegetarians.
素食者?看着我
Vegetarians? Look at me.
你看我这体魄 宝贝 我现在宛如新生
Look at all this man, baby. I'm brand new.
我需要动物糖分来生存
I need animal sugars to survive.
宝贝
Well, baby...
我留了沙拉给你
I have a salad for you.
沙拉?!
A salad?
特丽莎 看来一切在你掌控之中 我的任务也完成了
Hey, T, looks like you got this under control. My tour of duty is done.
再见 克莉斯丁 再见 迈克 再见 两位
Bye, Christine. Bye, Mike. Bye, guys.
迈克 等一下
Hey, Mike. Wait up. Wait up, wait up.
你打算做什么?你能帮我跑腿吗?
What you about to do? Can you run a quick-quick for me?
好 你需要什么?
Yeah, what you need?
我会给你$1000买一些彩虹糖
I'll give you $1,000 for some Skittles.
马克斯 我不会买糖给你
Marcus, I am not buying your ass no candy, man.
好 $2000 迈克 买叮当蛋糕 这就是我的最终报价
Okay, $2,000, Mike, for some Ding Dongs. And that's my final offer.
你别想有叮当了
I think you're gonna be Ding Dong-less...
就如我的灵魂一样
like my soul.
你总是带走我爱的人
You always take whoever I love.
我是迈克·劳瑞警探
This is Detective Mike Lowrey.
警监倒下了
The Captain is down.
他是我儿子
He's my son.
你的家庭一团糟 迈克
You got a fucked up family, Mike.
突发新闻 司法部一直对迈阿密警察局的贪污问题进行调查
The Department of Justice has been investigating the corruption in the Miami Police Department.
现在我们拥有可靠的情报
And we now have credible intelligence
当年是康拉德霍华德警监指挥这些人员
that Captain Conrad Howard was directing these elements
与贩毒集团协调
in coordination with the cartels.
不 我没兴趣 大概的时间
No, I'm not interested in approximately what time.
我只要知道确实 时间 明白吗?
I need to know exactly what time, do you understand?
你一直知道这件事?
You knew about this?
我两个星期前才知道
I found out two weeks ago.
记者会 真的吗?
A press conference. Really?
我很遗憾你们通过这种方式得知
I'm sorry about the way you had to find out.
但考虑到你们的密切关系 我们的密切关系?
But given your closeness-Our closeness?
如果没有霍华德警监 你们谁也没有工作
Neither one of y'all would have a job if it wasn't for Captain Howard.
丽塔 你知道事情不是这样的
Rita, you know this is not true.
坦白说 我不知道
Honestly, I don't.
调查发现了新的证据
The investigation has turned up new evidence.
迈阿密执法部门多年来出了不少岔子
Miami law enforcement's been a leaky ship for years now.
证人死亡 线人失踪
Witnesses turn up dead, informants disappear.
事件看起来是随机的 直到你汇总几年内发生的事
Events appear random until you aggregate them over a period of years.
然后就会看见一种模式
Then a pattern emerges.
他是谁?
Who is this?
巴德格莱斯 联邦调查局局长 此次调查组的领导
Bud Grice, FBI, heading up the JTF on this show.
这就是我
That's who I am.
我们知道有人在提供情报
Now, we knew someone was providing intelligence
给运毒品到南佛罗里达州的毒贩
to a cartel moving product into South Florida.
我们只是不知道是谁
We just didn't know who.
两周前 一名毒品集团的银行家被女友枪杀身亡
A cartel banker turned up dead two weeks ago, shot by his girlfriend.
他们找到一部手机 上面有霍华德的联系方式
They found a phone with Howard's contact on it.
与毒贩多年的沟通 还有海外银行账户信息
Years of communication with the cartel, account references offshore.
在霍华德的名下有数百万美元
Millions in Howard's name.
通过这些证据 终于可以给那贪腐的混蛋定罪了
Final piece we needed to nail that dirty motherfucker.
格莱斯!噢 哇 听我说
Grice! Oh, whoa. Hey, hey, let me holler at you.
你知道他倒下时我就在他身边 对吗?
You know I was with him when he went down, right?
你再说他贪腐试试
Call him dirty one more time.
你有种就说
I dare you.
我们知道还有其他人和他一伙 我们也会找到他们
We know he had others who were with him. We're gonna find them too.
和他一伙的人是我
I was with him.
现在就给我上手铐 我当时和他在一起 迈克
Put the cuffs on me right now. I was with him. Mike.
不 这些混蛋认为他死了 无法替自己辩护
No, these motherfuckers think that just 'cause he's dead and can't defend hisself,
就把所有问题推到他身上 毁了他的传奇
they gon' dump all this shit on him, burn his legacy.
有我在就不行
Not on my watch.
我是朱迪霍华德 美国法警
This is Judy Howard, US Marshals.
我知道我在这里没有管辖权
I realise I have no jurisdiction here.
但出于职业礼貌
But as a professional courtesy,
我想申请了解针对我父亲的指控的来源
I'd like to request visibility into the sources of the allegations against my father.
朱迪
Judy.
我们会解决这问题的 好吗?
We're gonna figure this shit out, all right?
凯莉还好吗?
How's Callie?
你觉得呢 迈克?
How do you think, Mike?
我们都在同一条船 朱迪
We're on the same team here, Judy.
当然不是 迈克
Like hell we are, Mike.
如果不是你的混蛋儿子 我爸爸应该还活着
My dad would still be alive if it weren't for your bastard son.
朱迪
Judy...
如果我在街上见到他 我以我父亲发誓
If I ever catch him out on the street, I swear on my father
我会杀了他
I will put him down.
我们走吧
Come on. Come on, man. Come on.
迈阿密警局
接下来该怎么办?
So, what's our next move?
他们说他和毒贩合作 我们去问毒贩吧
They said he was working with the cartel. Let's ask the cartel.
联邦监狱 佛罗里达州中部
你好吗?
How you doin'?
这里是监狱
It's prison.
是的
Yeah.
听好 我们需要你的帮忙
Look. We need your help.
他们说霍华德警监贪污
They're saying that Captain Howard was dirty.
你是否有情报?
Do you know anything about that?
这个情报能让我减刑多少?我还在争取
How much time I get off for this one? I'm still working on that.
我在告诉你 我需要你的帮忙
This is me telling you that I need you.
我需要知道霍华德警监是否与贩毒集团合作
I need to know if Captain Howard was working with the cartels.
没有
No.
他正在调查那些有合作的人
He was onto the ones that were.
所以他被追杀
So he got greenlit.
等等 不
Wait, no.
不 霍华德警监被杀是因为他在你母亲的暗杀名单上
No, Captain Howard was killed because he was on your mother's hit list.
他是被加上去的
He was added to it.
你们的人希望看起来像我们做的一样
Your people wanted it to look like us.
你们希望他死去
Your people wanted him dead.
你说"我们的人"是什么意思?
Whatchu mean, "our people"?
你应该小心
You should be careful.
你在玩游戏 但你连规则都不知道
You're playing a game and you don't even know the rules.
你那边有卑鄙的玩家 你乱说
There's dirty players on your side. That's bullshit.
等等 是谁?
Wait, who?
我见过他一次
I saw him one time.
你能认出他吗?是的
Can you ID him? Sí.
给我名字
Give me a name.
我不知道他的名字
I don't know his name.
我母亲
My mother.
她就是与他对接的人
She's the one who dealt with him.
我就知道我们该让那巫女活着
I knew we should have kept that damn witch alive.
马克斯
Marcus.
愿她安息
May she rest in peace.
老兄
Dude.
嘿 老板
Hey, boss.
迈阿密市警察局
我们的线人在联合特遣部队档案中 拿到了霍华德的所有记录
Our man on the inside got all of Howard's records in the JTF file.
电脑 手机 文件 一切所有
Computers, phones, files, all of it.
我们知道霍华德曾调查我们的行动
Well, we know Howard was onto our operation.
我们只是不知道他查到多少 别错过任何线索
We just don't know how much he had. We need to make sure we got every trace.
很好
That's beautiful.
嘿 老板
Hey, boss.
都是纸质文件 到目前为止都没问题
It's all the paper files. They're clean so far.
两个手机没问题 他办公室电脑是空的
Two phones had nothing. His office computer was empty.
他很小心 但是?
He was careful. But?
但他的旧个人笔记本电脑加密程度较弱
But his old personal laptop had weak encryption.
有了
Here we go.
网络故障
你说“我们”是什么意思?
Shit. We tripped a fail-safe.
你是"我们"是什么意思?
The fuck you mean, "we"?
某些东西被发送了
Something was sent.
给谁?
To who?
短信[已发送] 现在正在追踪电话
Tracing the phone now.
霍华德警监
搞什么?
What the hell?
他正在从另一世界给我们发短信
He's texting us from the other side.
不 他没有 马克斯
No, he's not, Marcus.
如果你看到这个
If you're seeing this...
我大概已经死了
I'm probably dead.
该死!
Fuck!
我真倒霉
Fuck me.
在我开始之前
Before I begin...
我想说一件事:
I wanna say one thing:
我正让你陷入致命的危险
I'm putting you in mortal danger.
各位
Boys...
我们组织内有内奸
we got rats in our walls.
但我必须确保你们是我的坏孩子
But I gotta make sure you're my bad boys.
可乐瓶巨人就是关键
The Coke-bottle giant is the key.
什么?
What?
别相信任何人
Don't trust anybody.
那是什么?什么意思?"可乐瓶巨人"
What's that? What does that mean? "The Coke-bottle giant."
弗莱彻
Fletcher.
完了
Oh, shit.
就是他们
These are the guys.
我们应该向这些混蛋开一枪 一次性解决它
We should put a bullet in these motherfuckers. Be done with it once and for all.
林茨 我爱你 任由你处置他们是最好的了
Lintz, I love you. I'd like nothing more than to let you loose on them.
但更多死去的警察对我们没有任何好处
But extra dead cops doesn't do us any favours here.
持续监视他们 看看他们是否有所行动
Keep them under constant surveillance and see if they make a move.
弗莱彻的仓库就在那条巷子
Fletcher's warehouse is right down that alley.
迈克 我没打算告诉你这件事
Mike, I wasn't even gonna tell you this.
那就别告诉我
Then don't tell me.
不 你一定要听 这很重要
No, you gotta hear this. This is big.
我死不了
I can't die.
什么?
What?
我死不了
I cannot die.
几周前你在我的婚礼上死得还不错
Motherfucker, you did a pretty good job of dying at my wedding a couple weeks ago.
但我没死
But I didn't.
看吧
Watch.
嘿 马克斯
Hey, Marcus.
喂!快!滚出马路!
Hey! Come on! Get out of the road!
喂!
Hey!
马克斯!
Hey! Marcus!
停
Hey, stop, stop.
马克斯!
Hey, hey! Marcus!
你这是疯了吗?
What are you, some kind of moron?!
停
Stop, stop, stop.
警察!停车!
Police! Stop!
喂!老兄!
Hey! Bro!
慢点!
Slow down!
斑马线!
Crosswalk!
跟我说话
Talk to me.
你要相信 迈克
You gotta trust, Mike.
相信自己 相信宇宙
Trust yourself. Trust the universe.
你够了 马克斯
Stop that shit, Marcus.
我的时间还没到 迈克
It's not my time, Mike.
好 你是说如果我对你的脸开枪
Oh, okay. So you're saying that if I shoot you in your face,
你是说你不会死
you're saying that you won't die.
命运注定你不会朝我脸上开枪
Fate dictates that you won't shoot me in the face.
我是说你说了
I'm saying... I'm... I'm saying that you saying
如果我对你的脸开枪 你不会死?
that if I shoot you in your face, are you saying you won't die?
命运不做假设 迈克
Fate doesn't deal in hypotheticals, Mike.
我要报警了
I'm gonna call the police.
他们已经到了 女士 别多管闲事
They're already here, ma'am. Mind your business.
到海滩去吧
Just go to the beach.
别再胡闹了 马克斯
Stop that shit, Marcus.
看吧?你把枪收起来了
See? You're putting your gun away.
他把枪收起来了
He's putting his gun away.
迈克
Ooh, Mike.
专心点
Focus, man.
我称这地方为黑人想象的创意空间
Yeah, I call this place, you know, Creative Space for Black Imagination.
弗莱彻
You know that... Fletcher.
我的天
Oh, my God.
谢谢你
Thank you.
这到底是什么地方?
What the hell is this place?
这是我的画廊工作室 我现在是一名艺术家
This is my studio gallery. I'm an artiste now.
拜托 你才不是艺术家
Please, you ain't no damn artist.
你们要什么?霍华德警监
What do you guys want? Captain Howard.
是 很遗憾听到他的遭遇 他改善了我的人生
Yeah. I was sorry to hear what happened to him. He helped turn my life around.
他叫我们找你谈
He told us to talk to you.
好 跟我谈
Okay. Talk to me.
我刚刚就和你谈了 那就说你该说的话
I just talked to you. Then say what you're supposed to say.
我已经说了我该说的话 你没有
I said what I'm supposed to say. You didn't.
那告诉我该说什么 我已经说了我能说的话
Then tell me what I'm supposed to say. I've said all I can say.
你在耍我们吗 豆秆?
Fucking with us, beanstalk?!
马克斯!别这样!
Marcus! Come on!
霍华德警监救了我的命 我不会搞砸这事的
Captain Howard saved my life. I'm not messing this up.
我不能说我该说的 直到你说了你该说的为止
I can't say what I supposed to say until you say what you supposed to say.
直接告诉我们你该说的话
Fletcher, just tell us what you supposed to tell us.
笨蛋 听好了
Dumbasses. Look.
霍华德警监正在调查一件大事
Captain Howard was onto something big.
他不相信你们这笨蛋会解决 所以他联络了我
He didn't trust that you dumb fucks would figure it out, so he contacted me.
因为你们很笨 而我是天才
Because you're stupid, and I'm a genius.
所以我用某个东西保护着那资料
So I protected the information in something.
用一个很美的东西
In something beautiful.
再动一下你的脸 再动一下!
Flex your face one more time. Flex it again!
我会打爆你的头
I will blow your fucking head off.
你能停吗?!拜托
Would you stop?! Come on.
在一个会永远活着的东西里面
In something that will live forever.
你开枪了?!
Did you shoot him?!
我不认为是我
I don't think so.
别动!
Freeze!
马克斯!
Marcus. Marcus!
你中枪了?
You hit?
没有
Nah-ah.
黑色软糖 没有人喜欢那玩意儿
Black jellybean. Nobody likes that shit.
哇
Whoa.
喂!停止那蠢事!
Hey! Stop that stupid shit!
我没跟你开玩笑!停!
I'm not fucking with you! Stop!
不要!
No! No, no! No! No!
我所向披靡!
I don't give a fuck!
马克斯!不要!
Marcus! No! No!
你在干什么?!
What are you doing?!
让我来!但你不行
I got this! But you don't, though.
不!
No. No!
马克!
Marc--!
走吧!我们走!
Let's go! Let's move!
马克斯!
Marcus!
伯内特和劳瑞在11街向北移动
Burnett and Lowrey are moving north on 11th.
迈阿密警察!快开!
Miami PD! Go!
你在干什么?我正在打击犯罪 宝贝!
What are you doing?! I'm fightin' crime, baby!
别动!
Freeze!
迈克!
Mike!
你以前有过恐慌发作吗?
Have you ever had a panic attack before?
什么?没人恐慌发作
What? Ain't nobody have no damn panic attack.
你的血压165/90了 出汗 恶心 看心理医生并不丢人
You're at 165 over 90. Sweaty. Nauseous. There's no shame in getting counselling.
好 谢谢你的关心 兄弟
All right. Thank you. Appreciate you, brother.
迈克 乖乖听医生的话
Mike, let the man do his job.
做得好
Good job, man.
嘿 迈克
Hey, Mike.
你为什么会恐慌?
What the hell you panicking about?
我不想说
I'm not speaking to you.
我做了什么?
What'd I do?
你们两个没事吧?
You two all right?
迈克恐慌发作
Mike had a panic attack.
他没有 迈克没事
He didn't. Mike is fine.
发生什么事?
What happened?
丽塔 你不会相信这件事 但我们收到一个信
Rita, you ain't gonna believe this shit. But we got a text--
一个线报 我们收到线报称弗莱彻违反了假释规定
A tip. We got a tip that Fletcher had violated his parole.
所以我们来这里
So we came down here
显然他陷入了一些与他无关的事
and obviously he was into some shit he ain't have no business.
是真的吗 马克斯?
Is that true, Marcus?
你知道我一直和迈克一起
Well, you know I was with Mike.
在所有人中 你怎么会认为霍华德警监做不法之事
How could you, of all people, think Captain Howard was dirty.
我不希望这是真的
I don't want this to be true.
但做好自己的事 遵循证据对大家都有好处
But it would benefit all of us to do our jobs and follow the evidence.
你认为他蠢到把账户记在自己名下
And you think he was stupid enough to put accounts in his own name.
他是被陷害的 被谁?
He's being framed. By who?
这就是我们想要找出的答案
That's what we're trying to find out.
丽塔 拜托 你不会那么傻
Rita, come on, you're smarter than this.
迈克 请别忘记你正和你的上司说话
Michael, please do not forget you're talking to your boss.
我在努力保护你
I'm trying to protect you here.
我们没有两个街区半径的录像
I got no footage for a two-block radius.
什么?
What?
他们肯定毁了所有闭路电视和安保摄像头
They must've killed all CCTV, all security cams.
我什么也找不到
I got nothing.
至少他们没拍摄到你的恐慌发作
At least they ain't film your panic attack.
各位
Hey, guys.
你恐慌发作了吗?没有
You had a panic attack? No.
你要的话 我能推荐一位好的辅导员 不用 东恩 谢谢
If you want, I can recommend a good counsellor. I'm good, Dorn. Thanks.
看 这是我拍的 一帧一帧看
Look, I shot this, went frame by frame.
看这个
Check it out.
好 不在这里
All right. Not here.
东恩 关了它 好
Dorn, shut it down. Yeah.
我们走
Hey. Let's go.
这是什么?
So, what is this?
我们不肯定
We're not exactly sure.
哇 哇
Whoa. Wow.
这就对了
There you go. There you go.
好 现在我知道是你们
All right, you fucks. Now that I know it's you...
是这样的:
here it is:
我不知道最高涉及到哪个高层 但我们这边有贪官
I don't know how high up it goes, but there's corrupt officials on our side.
而且他们和贩毒团合作
And they're working with the cartel.
大约九年前 这一切开始变得很奇怪
This all started smelling funny about nine years ago.
我们准备突袭的那批毒品失踪了
That shipment of coke we were about to raid went missing.
上头一直阻挡我
You know, I kept getting shut down from above.
所以我找了已退休的桑切斯和鲁伊斯
So I pulled Sanchez and Ruiz outta retirement.
我让他们从旁调查
I had 'em working on the outside, you know?
一周后 他们在一场车祸中丧生
They were killed in a car crash a week later.
这让我很震惊
That shook me up.
所以我从未让你们俩插手
And it's why I never brought you two in.
你们原本可以救我 我却担心你们的安全 真丢脸
Well, shame on me for worrying about your asses when you coulda saved mine.
但现在由你们决定
But now it's up to you.
还记得2003年的逮捕行动吗?
Remember the bust back in 2003?
142公斤摇头丸?
314 pounds of ecstasy?
我收在储存柜 没有记录在案
Well, I held onto the storage unit, off the books.
那就是真正的文件所在的地方
That's where the real files are.
消灭这些混蛋所需的一切
Everything you need to exterminate these rat fucks.
都在里面!
It's in there!
你们必须完成我无法做到的事
You're gonna have to finish what I couldn't.
拜托你们
Please.
拜托了 两位
Please, boys.
你们是我最后的希望
You're my last hope.
2003年
2003.
那是海地人 佐伊庞德
That was the Haitians. Zoe Pound.
他们的储物柜在哪里?
Where was their storage locker?
我不知道
I have no idea.
好 你们该去警察局调出我们的案卷原件档案
All right. We need you guys to go down to the station and pull our original case files.
我们就能找出储物柜在哪里
That'll tell us where the locker is.
低调并小心地做 我们不知道谁可以信任
Do it quietly and be careful. We don't know who we can trust.
这可是大件事
Shit, this is heavy, man.
我有些很重要的事要说
I just got something important to say.
我就直接说吧 澄清一下
I'm just gonna come out with it. Clear the air.
那个内奸不是我
The rat is not me.
谢谢你 东恩
Thanks for that, Dorn.
我觉得安全多了
I feel safer.
高度设防监狱活动操场
他们刚打算杀了我儿子
They just tried to kill my son.
因为阿曼多可以证明霍华德警监是无辜的
Because Armando can prove that Captain Howard was innocent.
警监去世前正在调查这些受贿的警官
Cap was onto these dirty players.
阿曼多告诉你的?
Armando told you that?
是的 这就是他们想杀死霍华德警监的原因
Yes. It's the reason they wanted Captain Howard dead.
阿曼多可以认出下令袭击警监的人
Armando can ID the guy that ordered the hit on Cap.
有名字吗?
He have a name?
没有 但知道对方长什么样
No. But a face.
我知道你们可以做到 好吗?
Listen, I know y'all can do this. All right?
转移阿曼多 带他去迈阿密 一个安全的地方
Just transfer Armando. Get him to Miami. Get him to a secure location.
我们审问他 拿到他的证词 给他一些照片
We'll debrief him. We'll get his testimony. We'll get some pictures in front of him.
但请马上去做
But please do it now.
这些人试图掩饰事实 而且他们不会停手
These guys are tryin' to cover their asses and they are not gonna stop.
这是为了霍华德警监
Do it for Captain Howard.
对霍华德警监不利的证据确凿无疑
Look, the evidence against Captain Howard is overwhelming.
如果我这样做 都是为了你
If I'm doing this, I'm doing it for you.
好 我们转移阿瑞塔斯吧
All right, let's transfer Aretas.
你陪他 把他带到迈阿密的冰屋 审问他
You'll accompany him, get him to igloo here in Miami, do a debrief.
但我是因为相信你 才会冒这么大风险
But I'm sticking my neck out and I'm trusting you.
如果他是骗人的 那我就完了
If he turns out to be bullshit, then it's gonna be my ass.
所以别把我害了 迈克
So don't screw me, Mike.
谢谢你
Thank you.
什么事?
Yeah?
我们找到了佐伊庞德的储物柜
We found Zoe Pound's storage unit.
我们去拿文件 然后收藏在我的船屋
We'll go get the files then take them to my houseboat for safekeeping.
好 继续 找到后告诉我
All right, stay on it. Let me know when you got it.
请交出你的枪支 枪械将于着陆后还给你
Please surrender your firearms. They will be returned to you upon touchdown.
你还好吗?
You good?
非常好
Never been better.
大约需要45分钟
It's about 45 minutes.
迈克 我没打算告诉你
Mike, I wasn't even gonna tell you this...
但在我们在一起的前世之一
but in one of our previous lifetimes together...
你曾是一只驴
you were a donkey.
而且我是你的主人
And I owned you.
你很固执 迈克
You were a stubborn ass, Mike.
你过去常咬人和吐口水
You used to bite and spit.
你很坏
You were nasty.
但我不是好主人 因为我总会打你
But I was a terrible owner, you know, because I used to beat you.
因为你不听话
Because you wouldn't listen for shit.
也许我打得让你感到羞耻 迈克
And maybe I beat some kind of shame into you, Mike.
现在我意识到我伤害了你的灵魂
And now I realise I was scarring your soul.
你错过了午睡?
You miss your nap?
迈克 我在尝试向你道歉
Mike, I'm trying to apologise to you.
你的小被子不在这里 但你可以闭眼休息
We don't have your blankie, but you could just rest your eyes.
你当驴子时就是这样 好吧
That's exactly how you was as a donkey. Mm-kay.
就是那副鬼样子 我明白了
That's that shit there. I get it.
你需要我帮忙系安全带吗?
You need some help with your seat belt?
不用 驴子
No, Donkey.
嘿 布莱恩特 我是布朗森
Hey. Bryant, this is Bronson.
其他人之后还要回去
Other guys are on turnaround.
坐好
Take a seat.
怎么了?
What's up?
自动驾驶仪
Read the lines.
读出来 "美国法警724航班 我们有紧急情况
"US Marshal flight 724, we have an emergency.
我们的囚犯在迈阿密警察劳瑞和伯内特的帮助下越狱了
Our prisoner has escaped custody with the aid of Miami PD Lowrey and Burnett.
这里有倒下的警员
There are officers down.
求救 他们冲着驾驶舱来了
Mayday, mayday. They are coming for the cockpit.
我重复 他们正在劫持CH-47
I repeat, they are hijacking the CH-47.
请所有地面单位回应"
All ground units please respond."
把劳瑞的枪给我 收到
Give me Lowrey's gun. Copy.
快走!
Go, go!
去找劳瑞
Get Lowrey.
我们走!
Let's go!
我们不惧暴风雨 王八
We welcome the storm, motherfu--!
把我从这该死的牢笼里救出来!
Get me out of this fucking cage!
马克斯!
Marcus!
迈克!
Mike!
太重了!
It's too heavy!
别放手!
Don't let go!
抓住驾驶杆!
Grab the stick!
你怎么会开飞机?
Where the hell you learn how to fly?!
我是个毒贩 向右!
I'm a drug dealer, man. To the right!
他用了我的枪
He was using my gun.
他们究竟是怎么登上美国法警直升机的?
How the hell did they get on a federal transport?
我们必须分头行动
We need to split up.
我们要在一起
We're gonna stay together.
谁说的?
Says who?
我不是在问你
I'm not asking you.
我在告诉你 我们要在一起
I'm telling you. We're stayin' together.
别挡我的路
Fuck outta my way.
嘿 哪里 放开我
Hey. Where--? Get the fuck off me.
喂!
Hey! Hey!
听好
Look.
你是唯一能指证幕后主使的人!
You are the only person who can identify whoever is doing this!
我们活下去的唯一方法 就是先抓住他们
The only way that any of us stays alive is if we get them before they get us.
根本没有我们!
There's no us! There is no us!
该死
Damn.
劳瑞的基因还真是让人头大
That Lowrey DNA is a bitch.
你俩的劲儿都这么大
Y'all some strong motherfuckers.
好 这样吧 大家放松 我数到三
Okay. Now, look, everybody unflex. On three.
一!二!
One! Two!
就是这样
There you go.
霍华德警监给我们留下了文件 这些文件会告诉我们是谁干的
Captain Howard left us files that's gonna tell us who's doin' this.
都在东恩那里
Dorn has 'em.
我们只需要回到迈阿密
We just have to get back to Miami.
你最好别拖慢我
You better not slow me down.
丢了你们的电话
Lose your phones.
你跟紧我 否则我就让你自生自灭
You keep up with me or I leave you in the dirt.
现在你已来到我的世界
You're in my world now.
迈克 我们必须想一想
Hey, Mike. Look, we gotta think about this.
我知道你要跟他走 因为他是你的"儿子"
I know you wanna move with him, you know, because he's your "son".
哇 别那样说
Whoa, whoa. Don't air quote that.
不 我没有 我只是说我知道你在尝试保护他
No, I didn't. I'm just sayin' I know why you tryin' to protect him.
因为他是"家人"
'Cause he "family".
你这样做和刚刚没什么差
Hey. Movin' the air quotes down to your hips doesn't un-air-quote them.
就直说他是我儿子吧
Just say he's my son.
他是你儿子 不
He's your son. No, no.
手掌向上就像你试图说噢 他其实不是我儿子
Palms up is like you tryin' to say, oh, he's not really my son.
噢 你儿子走掉了
Oh. Well, your son's gettin' away.
混蛋
Shit.
如果你的人在执行某任务 最好通知我们
If your men are on some kind of op, you might wanna pull us in.
不然 这对他们来说不太好
Otherwise, it doesn't look good for them.
朱迪
Judy.
尸体的身份都确认了?对 但有三人下落不明
You ID the bodies? Roger. We got three unaccounted for.
劳瑞 伯内特和阿雷塔斯
Lowrey, Burnett and Aretas.
这些混蛋 该死
Motherfuckers. Fucking--!
见鬼
Shit.
好 听好了!
All right. Listen up!
我们有三名嫌疑人 他们都携带武器 而且很危险
We have three suspects, armed and dangerous, out there.
给我把他们抓回来
And I want them back.
我们走!
Let's go!
等等 朱迪
Hold on. Judy.
三个 嫌疑人?
Three suspects?
你觉得这里发生什么事?
What do you think is happening here?
你觉得呢?
What do you think?
播放音频
Play the audio.
美国法警724航班 我们有紧急情况
US Marshal flight 724, we have an emergency.
我们的囚犯在迈阿密警察劳瑞和伯内特的帮助下越狱了
Our prisoner has escaped custody with the aid of Miami PD Lowrey and Burnett.
有警官倒下 求救
There are officers down. Mayday, mayday.
不是吧 你不会相信迈克和马克斯会这样做
Come on, you can't possibly believe Mike and Marcus would do this.
你自己说的 劳瑞一心想让儿子出狱
Nah, you said it. Lowrey was obsessed with getting his son out of prison.
别急 朱迪
Slow down, Judy.
这里不是迈阿密 塞卡达
This isn't Miami, Secada.
这些都是我的逃犯 现在全世界都是我的管辖范围
These are my fugitives and right now the whole world is my jurisdiction.
你们认识了一辈子 你怎么能这么说?
You've known them your whole life. How can you even suggest--?
我认为这是迈克和马克斯策划的吗?
Do I think that Mike and Marcus planned this?
也许不是
Probably not.
但当涉及到家人时 人们会做他们通常不会做的事
But people do things they wouldn't normally do when family's involved.
根据我的经验 无辜的人不会逃跑
In my experience innocent men don't run.
我们能不能先分析 你能不能做好自己的工作?
Can we stop and think before-Are you capable of doing your job?
因为我必须继续调查
'Cause I need to move on.
他们还活着
They survived.
什么意思?
What the fuck you mean, they survived?
现场没有尸体 美国法警将其视为搜捕行动
No bodies on site. US Marshals are treating it as a manhunt.
这些人就是死不了
These guys just refuse to die.
他们是通缉犯
They're wanted men.
执法部门和媒体现在是我们的朋友
Law enforcement and media are our friends now.
三名逃犯的追捕行动
A manhunt for three fugitives
在南佛罗里达州引起了轩然大波
is sending shock waves across South Florida.
弹道报告与从尸体中找到的子弹相符
Ballistic reports have matched the bullets recovered from the bodies...
鉴于最近发生的事件 您打算退出市长竞选吗?
Are you planning on dropping out of the mayor's race in light of the recent events?
目前搜捕工作正在进行中
The manhunt is currently underway.
联邦调查局正在协助美国法警逮捕这些人
The FBI is assisting US Marshals in bringing these men in.
劳瑞 伯内特和阿雷塔斯应被视为有武器且危险
Lowrey, Burnett and Aretas should be considered armed and dangerous.
这些人杀害了其他专业执法人员
These are individuals who have killed fellow law enforcement professionals.
如果你看到什么 请说出来
If you see something, say something.
在道上悬赏
Put a bounty on the streets.
通知城里的每一个帮派 让他们为之而战
Get it to every gang in the city and let them fight for it.
五百万
Five mil.
我们去把这些混蛋抓起来
Let's go get these motherfuckers.
宇宙太疯狂了 不是吗?
The universe is crazy, ain't it?
看我们
Look at us.
今早起床时没人料到我们会走到这一步吧
I bet none of us thought when we woke up today this is where we'd be.
你离开了监狱
You outta jail.
我俩要进监狱了
We goin' to jail.
命运真幽默
This shit is special.
迈克?
Mike?
你有什么想对阿曼多说的吗?
Is there anything you would like to say to Armando?
你怎么那样说呢?没有
Fuck you talkin' to me like that? No.
迈克 就是现在 向你儿子说出来
Mike, this is a moment. Express with your son.
对不起
I'm sorry.
这样就对了嘛
That's what I'm talking about.
为了什么?为了一切
For what? For everything, man.
看来我爱的人都遭遇坏事 所以
Seems like bad shit happens to anybody I love, so...
我开始想也许我被诅咒了
Startin' to think maybe I'm cursed.
我只是觉得
I just feel like...
也许是我连累了你
maybe I cursed you.
你没有
You ain't fuckin' cursed me.
大家都会遇上不好的事
Bad shit happens to everybody.
从来都不是你一个人的事
Ain't always about you.
阿曼多
Hey, Armando.
不知我是否跟你说过 但几个星期前我死了
I don't know if I told you this, but I died a couple of weeks ago.
很遗憾听到这个消息
Sorry to hear about that.
噢 不 是我经历过的最好的事情
Oh, no. The best thing that ever happened to me.
那次经历太不可思议
Shit's wild.
但你们?
But y'all?
你们就是我活过来的理由
Y'all the reason I came back.
嘿
Hey.
大家 抱一个
Everybody, bring it in.
来 抱一个 来吧
Come on, bring it in. Come on.
什么?
What?
这就对了 阿曼多
There you go, Armando.
这就对了 这就
There you go. There you--
你俩这逃犯当得太不合格了
Y'all are some terrible fuckin' fugitives.
你以为自己是马克斯温弗瑞吗?
So, what are you, fuckin' Marcus Winfrey?
什么?看吧?
What? Now, see?
你让我们看起来很软弱 好像不知如何逃跑
You makin' us look soft, like we don't know how to be on the run.
第二修正案才是美国自己的国土安全部
最好先给你找一身别的衣服穿
Better get you out of this.
喂!
Hey!
那孩子真固执 就像他父亲一样
That boy hard-headed. Chip off the old block.
瞧瞧我发现了什么
Well, what we got here?
该隐 过来看看!
Hey, Cain, come take a look at this!
你们这些小伙子在干什么?
What are you boys doin'?
"小伙子"?
"Boys"?
你们在偷我们的衣服?看起来是这样
Are y'all stealing our clothes? Looks like it.
种族主义
Fuckin' racism.
就因为我们是黑人 你们就觉得我们偷了你们的烂东西?
Y'all think just because we Black we stealin' your shit?
这些是我自己的黑人服装
Now, these are my own Black clothes
今天我从我的黑人衣柜穿上的
that I put on today from my own Black closet.
马克斯!什么?
Marcus! What?
看你衣服上写了什么
Look at your shirt.
纯种白人男孩
这东西怎么会在我的黑人衣柜?
How'd this get in my Black closet?
不如你给我们唱一首瑞芭的歌
Why don't you boys sing us a little Reba song.
瑞芭?瑞芭?好
Reba? Reba? Oh, yeah.
请
Oh, please.
那 因为他介绍瑞
That's-'Cause he put... He put me on to Reb--
哪一首?你们想听哪首?
Which one? Which y'all--? Which one?
唱你最爱的
Sing your favourite.
她有很多 因为她有许多热门歌曲
Oh, she got plenty of them. 'Cause she got hits.
是快节奏的歌吗?还是慢的?对 记得那首吗?
Was it the up-tempo song? Or the slow jam? Yeah, yeah, remember the one?
是那首慢的 哥们 噢 好
It was the slow one, nigga. Oh, okay.
早上你伤害了我是的 因为她受伤了
You hurt me in the morning Yes, 'cause she was hurt.
晚上你伤害了我对了
You hurt me at night Yes, yes.
但我已改变改变
But I've changed Changed
我很坚强 我是个女人
And I'm strong I'm a woman
我是个坚强的黑女
I'm a strong Black wom--
我是个坚强的女人
I'm a strong woman
是的 因为她不是黑人
Yeah, 'cause she's not Black.
然后
And then...
你该怎么办?
What you gonna do?
你该怎么
What you gonna d--?
那不是瑞芭的歌
That ain't no Reba song.
这是她的混音带里的
It's from her mixtape.
混蛋!
Goddamn it!
对不起!我们会还回来!
We're sorry! We'll bring it back!
我们没有因为我们是黑人而偷你的东西!
We're not stealing your shit because we Black!
你是否爱过她?
Did you ever love her?
什么?
What?
我妈妈 你是否爱过她?
My mother. You ever love her?
他正在表达
He's expressing.
我肯定爱过她
I definitely loved her.
然后你出卖了她
And then you sold her out.
我做错了
I made some mistakes.
我也是你的错误
Like me.
你知道我不是 等等 阿曼多
You know that is not what I was trying-Now wait a damn minute, Armando.
他正在努力弥补
He's trying to make up for it.
他不欠你什么
He don't owe you a damn thing.
好 等等 马克斯 你太严厉了
All right, hold on. Hold on, Marcus. You're just... You're being aggressive.
我做爸爸很久了 他必须听的 迈克
I've been a dad a long time. He needs to hear this, Mike.
他需要一些严厉的爱
He needs some tough-ass love.
阿曼多 也许他确实亏欠了你
Armando. Maybe he does owe you something. Okay?
你妈被他骗了
Your mom being deceived by him.
你出生在布满谎言的监狱里
You being born in prison, in a web of lies
这使你变成一个冷血杀手
that turned your ass into a stone-cold fuckin' killer.
是的 你是一个杀手
Yeah. You're a killer.
但这男人由始至终是真诚的
But this man, through it all, has been nothing but solid.
那是什么年度之父的废话
That's some father-of-the-year shit right there.
是吗?
Is it?
你那很烂的教养方式把卡车弄坏了
Your wack-ass parenting broke the truck.
我的错
My bad.
是的 坏了
Yeah, nah, that's dead.
我们离塔比莎的夜店不远
We're not far from Tabitha's.
不 迈克 你知道那女人是疯的
No, Mike. You know that woman's crazy.
没错 但她喜欢我
Yeah, but she likes me.
我不认为她有你想的那么喜欢你
I don't think she likes you as much as you think.
小马离这里大约两英里 小马是什么?
The Pony's about two miles from here. What's The Pony?
我需要我的IG Friendster 更多的性爱
I need my Instagram. I need my Friendster. I need more sex.
我需要更多男人涌入这个夜店
I need more men in this club.
你们都很美 快去上班
You all look beautiful. Now get back to work.
迈克·劳瑞 竟然是你
Mike Lowrey. Damn.
你好吗 塔比莎?
What up, Tabitha?
你们有麻烦对吧?
So y'all in trouble, huh?
是的 我们需要帮忙
Yeah, we need some help.
我们需要一些衣服可不是嘛
We need some clothes. No shit.
一辆车和几部手机
A ride and some phones.
是 还有一些枪
Yeah. Guns too.
那是我儿子 阿曼多
That's my son. That's Armando.
你有一个西班牙小儿子?
You got you a little Spanish son?
是的 说来话长
Yeah, it's a long story.
你能帮我们吗?
Can you hook us up?
你要的我都有 但你能给我什么?
I mean, I got all that but what you gonna do for me?
什么意思?我们会付钱
What you mean? We good for that.
你本来可以
You were.
但你们现在是逃犯 所以
But you guys are men on the run now, so...
你需要什么?
Well, what you need?
我需要什么?
What I need?
我要你取悦我
I need you to eat this pussy.
我不做 知道吗?
I'm not doin' that, all right?
哇 等等 迈克 你想想
Whoa, hold on, Mike, hold on. Think about this.
你说枪和手机对吗?
Now, you say guns and phones, right?
这样吧 你也知道迈克结婚了
Okay, well, look, you know Mike's a married man.
所以呢?
So?
所以他需要一些合理的推诿
So he's gonna need some plausible deniability.
我要你躺下来 伸出你的舌头
So I'mma have you lay down and stick out your tongue.
接下来由你来做
And you gonna have to do the rest.
我可以那样做
I can fuck with that.
继续 宝贝 不 马克斯
Oh, yeah, go on, baby. No, Marcus.
你只需要闭上眼睛 迈克 不行!
All you gotta do is close your eyes, Mike. No!
我需要照片 你会拍照吧?
I'mma need pictures. You know how to take pictures, right?
我们没时间了 请你别再开玩笑
Hey. We don't have a lot of time. I need you to stop fuckin' around.
我没有开玩笑
Oh, I'm not fuckin' around.
好 我们走
All right, hey, let's go.
等一下
Wait, hold up.
坐下
Sit your motherfuckin' ass down.
塔比莎 你在做什么?你 在做什么?
Hey, Tabitha, what is you doin'? What is you doin'?!
坐下!你们都坐下!
Sit your married ass down! You get y'all asses down too!
完了 大家坐下
Shit. Everybody sit down.
坏孩子在我这里 我们去领钱吧
Hey, I got the bad boys right here. Let's get that money.
塔比莎 闭嘴
Hey, Tab. Shut the fuck up.
等等 我不明白
Hold up, I'm confused.
你不要他舔你?
You didn't want him to licky-licky?
你的人头有五百万美元悬赏金
There's a $5 million bounty on your head.
我需要那笔钱 我只是在拖延
I need that money. I was just stalling.
太贱了 他差点就做了
That's... That's cold. He almost did that shit.
才没有 马克斯
He did not, Marcus.
我说了她不喜欢你
I told you she didn't like you.
起身
Get the fuck up.
悬赏不要求你们活着
The bounty is dead or alive.
别犯傻
Don't be stupid.
阿曼多
Hey, Armando.
如果你活下来 我会让你
If you live, I'll let you...
什么?
What?
我说如果你活下来 来找我
I said if you live, motherfucker, holler at me.
他有点可爱
He was kinda cute.
我们收到一个举报
We got a tip.
确认是我们的逃犯
Positive ID on our fugitives.
行动开始
Let's do this.
迈克 我打算开始行动
Mike, I'm about to make my move.
不行 跟着这些人走就是了
No, the fuck you're not. You about to go wherever these men are taking us.
我不去
Oh, I'm not goin'.
前面三个我来处理 后面六个由你处置
Now I'll take the three in the front, you take the six in the back.
马克斯 我们没有任何武器
Marcus, we do not have any weapons.
倒数五 四 三
In five... four... three...
该死!
Fuck!
糟了!是这王八蛋
Ah, shit! This motherfucker.
混蛋 你想干什么?
Fuckboy, fuckboy Whatcha gonna do?
迈克!
Ayo, Mike!
小白兔拿枪可没趣了是吧?
Ain't no fun when the rabbit got the gun, huh?
等等 你认识这人?
Wait, you know this guy?
是的 几年前我用锤子打了他
Yeah, I hit him with a hammer a couple years ago.
你以为我忘了曼尼牛排店的那件事?
You think I forgot about that fucking ho shit you pulled off at Manny's Prime Rib?
我怎么让你们两个抓住我的?
How the fuck did I let you two catch me?
迈克 我要我的五百万
Mike, I want my five million.
马克斯!
Marcus!
我把我兄弟们都带来了 整个帮派都在!
You see I got the fam with me. The streets!
我们可以轻松简单地完事 否则就开战!
We could do this nice and easy or we can go to war!
因为我准备开战了!
'Cause I'm fucking war-ready!
你在干什么?
What are you doing?!
不!
No!
快走!
Go, go, go, go!
退后!
Back up! Back up! Back up!
不!
No! No!
挡风玻璃雨刷液是易燃的!
Windshield wiper fluid is flammable!
我怎么知道?!我又不是科学家!
How the hell am I supposed to know that?! I ain't no damn scientist!
大家冷静 火在外面
Everybody relax. The fire's on the outside.
糟了!
Oh, shit!
现在到里面了!
Now it's on the inside!
完了!
Shit!
好吧
Okay.
大家出去!
Everybody out! Everybody out!
混蛋
Shit.
开门!
Open the damn door!
我们感觉到你在那边 小子 开门
We can feel you right there, boy. Open the door.
嘿!
Hey!
开门 肌肉奶
Open up, Muscle Milk.
拜托 你在干什么?
Come on, man. What the fuck is you doing?
没什么 我现在不太方便
Nothing. It's just not a great time for me right now, guys.
我们现在也不太方便
It's not a great time for us either.
大约一个小时后我们再见面
Okay, let's reconvene in like an hour or so.
宝贝 沐浴露没了
Babe, we're out of body wash.
不是吧?
What the hell?
我们找到你们了
We found you guys.
我们在恋爱 好吗?
We're in a relationship. Okay?
好
Oh, okay. All right.
我无法忍受偷偷摸摸
Sneaking around has been destroying me.
我们是几个月前在一起的 这不会影响我们的本职工作
It started about a couple months ago. It will not affect our professional lives.
除了在货车上那一次
Except for that one time in that van.
我不会道歉的 没什么好道歉的
I am not sorry. Nothing to be sorry about.
你知道的 人们会做那种事
Yeah, you know. I mean, people do that shit.
你们没事吧?我们很好 我想
Are you guys okay? Yeah, we're good. I wanted to--
搞什么?好 哇
What the fuck?! Okay. Whoa, whoa.
卡丽
Hey, Kelly. Kelly.
我叫你在外面等一下
I asked you to wait outside for a second.
别激动 卡丽 他和我们是一伙的
All right. Kelly, he's with us.
他不能在这里
He can't be here.
这是我儿子 阿曼多
This is my son, Armando.
我知道他是谁 所以他不能在这里
I know who he is, and that's why he can't be here.
我很相信你 迈克 但我肯定不相信他
I trust you with my life, Mike. But I as sure as shit don't trust him.
我相信他
I trust him.
那带他去你家
Then take him to your house.
迈克 让我和她谈谈好吗?
Hey, Mike. Can I have a second with her, please?
好的 请便
Yeah, yeah. Please.
亲爱的 放轻松
Hey, sweetie. Relax. Relax.
过来一下
Come here for a sec. Come over here for a second.
我们俩都有可能坐牢
We could both end up in jail.
给他一个机会 对 给他一个机会杀光我们?
Give him a chance. Yeah, give him a chance to kill us all?
这事超出常规了
This is some dysfunctional shit.
她没事了 看起来不像
She's fine. She don't look fine.
我没事了 是 没错
I'm fine. Yes, you are.
你说什么?好
The fuck you say? All right, all right.
是语言文化差异 他说的是英语
It's the language barrier. It was English.
肯定是英语
It was definitely English.
谢谢你的衣服
Thanks for the drip.
好 我们正在汇总所有数据
Yeah. Okay, we're aggregating all the data.
有超过100小时的视频 200多个音频单元
There's over 100 hours of video, 200 units of audio.
我们正在索引所有音频 视频和地理定位IP网络数据
We're indexing all audio, video and geo-located IP network data
创建视野图并制定目标区
to create a sight picture and develop a target package.
基本上 要仔细筛选来找到那混蛋
Basically, you sifting through all this shit to find the guilty motherfucker.
没错
Bingo.
东恩
Hey, Dorn.
你能安全地让我进入Ring程序吗?我想看看家人
Can you safely get me into my Ring app? I wanna see my family.
好 我们有自己的VPN和路由器 你的用户名是什么??
Yeah, we got our own VPN and router. What's your username?
马克斯37
Marcus37.
密码?
And password?
士力架89
Snickers89.
我很快就能回家了 宝贝
Almost home, baby.
我们开工吧 这里有很多事要做
Hey, let's get to work. We got a lot to get through here.
我们到底要找什么?
So, what exactly are we looking for?
我们正在寻找下令袭击警监的人
We're looking for the guy who ordered the hit on Cap.
阿曼多可以认出他
Armando can ID him.
这个混蛋就是我的白鲸
This fucking bastard has been my white whale.
过去的九年 我一直想用鱼叉刺死这个王八蛋
For the last nine years, I've been trying to harpoon the son of a bitch.
但现在看你们的了
But now it's up to you.
难道我走进你家 教你如何做毒品?
Ey-Ey-Ey. Do I walk into your house and show you how to make cocaine?
将它放大
Blow it up.
是他
It's him.
你肯定?
You sure?
就是那个下令袭击的人
That's the guy that ordered the hit.
找到名字了
Bam. Got a name.
詹姆斯麦格拉思 陆军游骑兵学校 反情报
James McGrath. Army Ranger School, counterintelligence.
2005年之前一直部署在墨西哥
Deployed in Mexico until 2005.
曾与缉毒局 国防部武官办公室合作
Worked with the DEA, Defence Attache's office.
糟了
Oh, shit.
他被你的朋友 贩毒集团扣为人质
He was taken hostage by your friends, the cartel.
他"在胁迫下"供出了整个小队
He gave up his entire squad "under duress".
这和酷刑无异啊
It's called torture, man.
整个小队只有他活了下来
He was the only survivor.
警监一直都有他的犯罪证据
Cap had him the whole time.
他只是不知道
He just didn't know it.
喂
Hello.
嘿 是我
Hey. It's me.
迈克 你在哪里?
Damn it, Michael. Where are you?
丽塔 我们要过来 我们有证据霍华德警监是无辜的
Rita, we're coming in. We got proof that Captain Howard is innocent.
什么证据?
What proof?
我们找到杀了霍华德警监的人
We got the guy that had Captain Howard killed.
阿曼多认出了他
Armando ID'd him.
也就是用直升机袭击我们的家伙 詹姆斯麦格拉思
Same dude that attacked us on the chopper. James McGrath.
丽塔 我们有多达十年的档案
Rita, we got ten years' worth of files.
警监死前一直在调查这些家伙 我们全部查到了 是一整个网络
Cap was investigating these dudes. We got 'em all. It's a whole network.
明天我们就会交给你
We'll surrender to you tomorrow.
好 我们该走了
Hey, look, we gotta go.
迈克 什么
Michael, what--?
你还好吗?
You okay?
他们会过来
They're coming in.
什么?
What?
迈克尔说他们有证据证明霍华德无罪
Michael says they have proof that exonerates Howard...
说明了一切
explains everything.
你是否还爱他?
Do you still love him?
什么?
What?
不
No.
但我相信他
But I believe him.
小心就是了 宝贝
Just be careful, babe.
我们还去吃晚餐吗?
Still going to dinner?
好的
Yeah.
他们找到档案了
They have the files.
我们要让这看起来像贩毒集团 只说西班牙语
We need to make this look like cartel business. Spanish only.
弹药准备好了 出发
Ammo's ready to go. Let's go.
触发动作传感器
我们只需要一名人质
We only need one hostage.
完了!
Shit! Shit! Shit!
各位!我们有麻烦
You guys! We got a problem.
迈阿密指挥中心 有罪犯入侵居民家中
Miami Central, Miami Central. 29 in progress.
糟了 那是我家
Oh shit, that's my house.
罪犯目标是同僚警察的家 请指示
Please advise, MOS residence.
立即回应
Respond forthwith.
该死 糟糕 不 糟了
Fuck. Oh, fuck. Oh, no.
快 克莉斯丁
Come on, Christine.
未知来电
该死 派一个警队去我家
Shit. Get a unit over to my house.
快啊 雷吉!接电话!
Come on, Reggie! Pick up! Pick up.
迈阿密指挥中心 又发生一起罪犯入侵事件
Miami Central, we have another 29 in progress.
请派警队到劳瑞警探的家庭住址
Please send units to Detective Lowrey's home address.
敌人倒下了!
Enemy's down!
雷吉!敌人正在逼近
Reggie! You got incoming.
带家人到安全的地方 什么?
Get the family to somewhere safe. What?
马上去!是 长官
Now! Yes, sir.
发生什么事?怎么了?
What's happening? What's going on?
有人闯进屋子 我要保护你们的安全
There's people comin' in the house. I gotta keep y'all safe.
请小心!
Please be careful!
雷吉 发生什么事?相信我 我爱你们
Okay, Reggie, what's happening? Okay. Trust me. I love you.
该死!要命!
Fuck! Fuck!
在你后面 雷吉!
Behind you, Reg!
天啊!
Oh, damn!
这人是谁呀?他是我儿子!
Who the fuck is this guy?! That's my boy! That's my boy!
好棒!
Damn!
加油
Come on, come on, come on.
不!
No, no, no!
天啊!
Holy shit!
加油!
Come on, come on!
天啊!
Holy shit!
把你们打得屁滚尿流 王八蛋们
Chitty-Chitty-Bang-Bang, motherfuckers.
我的零食就是你的 雷吉
Me snacks is your snacks, Reggie.
好了 进去吧
All right, come on.
迈克 你看到吗?
Mike, did you see that shit?
接电话
Pick up the phone.
哇 迈克!
Whoa, Mike! Mike! Mike!
等一下
One second.
凯莉
Callie.
我在电视上看到 我妈妈正在追捕迈克叔叔
I saw it on TV. My mom is after Uncle Mike.
他不可能做了他们所说的一切
There is no way that he did everything that they're saying.
亲爱的
Sweetheart.
一切会好起来的
Everything is going to be okay.
知道吗?
Okay? Okay?
喂?是我 离开房子
Hello? It's me. Get out of the house.
凯莉和我一起 带她走!马上离开!
I've got Callie with me. Take her and go! Get out now!
凯莉 到我后面去
Callie, get behind me.
迈克
Mike.
克莉斯丁!
Christine!
劳瑞先生
Mr Lowrey.
我在跟谁说话?
Who am I speaking to?
我想你知道我是谁
I think you know who you're speaking to.
我要你儿子
I need your boy...
以及你敬爱的警监所藏匿的所有证据
and whatever evidence your beloved captain had squirrelled away.
用这些交换你的妻子
And for that, you can have your wife.
稍后我会回电教你怎么做
I'll call you back with instructions.
混蛋
Aw, shit.
该死的
Goddamn it.
我会去
I'll go.
让我的生命有价值一些
Let my life be worth something.
绝对不行
Never.
迈克
Mike.
他已经知道了
He knew.
什么意思?
What do you mean?
他已经知道我们会来
He knew we were comin' in.
他已知道我们有霍华德警监的档案
He knew we had Captain Howard's files.
他知道我们认出他
He knew we had ID'd him.
他怎么会知道?
How?
唯一与你交谈过的人是丽塔
Only person you spoke to was Rita.
不是丽塔
It's not Rita.
她对男人的品味也太差了
Damn, she got bad taste in men.
未知来电
司法部一直在调查迈阿密警察局的腐败问题
Justice has been investigating the corruption in the Miami Police Department...
有报告称已故警监康拉德·霍华德
...with reports suggesting the late Captain Conrad Howard...
喂?
Hello?
指挥着这些人员与毒贩协调
...was directing these elements in coordination with the cartels.
对霍华德的指控 间接针对劳瑞和伯内特
Allegations against Howard, which allude to include Lowrey and Burnett,
包括帮助毒贩将毒品运到佛罗里达州
and the operation range from helping cartels move the product into the state of Florida
以及交出关键证人 销毁证据
as well as giving up key witnesses, destruction of evidence,
甚至谋杀同事
and even the murder of fellow officers.
发生什么事?我不知道
What's going on? I don't know.
案件有了突破 我必须去警局
There's been a breakthrough in the case. I need to get down to the station.
我要到那里去
I'm gonna head down there.
我跟你去
I'm coming with you.
你在发短信给谁?
Who are you texting?
我需要和办公室联系
Just... Just gotta get in touch with the office.
联合部队
JTF.
必须通知大家
Gotta let everybody know.
亲爱的 别这样
Hey. Honey. Come on.
亲爱的 你在干什么?停手
Honey, what are you doing? Stop that.
你在干什么?停手
What are you doing? Stop it.
放开我 你在干什么?
Let go of me. What are you doing?
还给我!
Give it back to me. Give it back!
见鬼
Fuck!
来
Hey, hey, come on.
你还好吗?
You okay?
看手机
Look at the phone.
你知道你完蛋了 对吧?
You know you done fucked up, right?
你没事吧?
You all right?
对不起
I'm sorry.
没什么好抱歉的
Ain't got nothing to be sorry for.
我们会找到她的 警监
We'll find her, boss.
除了在场的人 我不相信任何人
I don't trust anybody that's not standing right here, right now.
我们每多牵扯进来一个人
Every extra person that we involve
都会增加他们知道我们要来的可能性
increases the likelihood that they know we're coming,
这增加了克莉斯丁和凯莉
which increases the likelihood that Christine and Callie
无法逃生的可能性
don't make it out of there.
这意味着不要特警 法警和后援
That means no SWAT, no marshals, no backup.
只有我们
It's just us.
我从来没想过事情会这样发展
I never meant for it to go this way.
你认为事情会如何发展?
How did you mean it to go?
9/11之后 没有人关心毒品进入这个国家
After 9/11, nobody cared about drugs coming into this country.
为了确保边境安全 我们开始与毒贩合作
So to secure the borders we started to work with the cartels.
他们随时警告我们任何即将发生的恐怖活动
And they kept us informed about any terrorist activity coming our way.
效果很好 从那以后我们就没有再受到袭击
And it worked. We haven't had an attack since.
我们正在保护这个国家
We were protecting this country.
你杀害警察并通过将毒品带入这个国家而致富
You were killing cops and getting rich putting drugs into this country.
丽塔 所以你才杀了霍华德
Rita. That's why you killed Howard.
他盯上你 你要掩饰你的罪行
He was onto you. You wanted to cover your tracks.
不 是麦格拉思
No. That was McGrath.
他失控了
He's out of control.
丽塔 先听我的
Rita. Just take a second.
我无意让这一切发展到这个地步
I never meant for any of this to go this way.
我想我只想知道你是否是真心的
I guess I just need to know if it was ever real.
我一直都是真心的
It was always real.
我慌了 失控了
I panicked. I lost control.
你是否爱过我?
Did you love me?
是的
Yes.
我发誓
I swear.
那表示
Well, that means...
很好 声音样本采集完成
We good. We got it.
99%声音匹配
99% voice match.
我完全不在乎 你这废物
...absolutely nothing to me, you piece of shit.
是我
Hey. It's me.
到底发生什么事?
What the hell's going on?
你搞砸了 就是这回事
You screwed up is what's going on.
我们暴露了 到了那里我会解释
We've been compromised. I'll explain when I get there.
我们要转移人质 古巴 长期禁锢
We're moving the hostages. Cuba. Long-term hold...
这样在我们解决这个问题时 劳瑞 伯内特和阿雷塔斯就不敢轻举妄动
to keep Lowrey, Burnett and Aretas quiet while we sort this out.
我会带来水上飞机 天一亮我就会到
I'm bringing a seaplane. I'll be there at first light.
好 把这个地方收拾起来
All right, pack this place up.
所有设备和人员准备搬迁
All equipment and personnel prepare to move.
我们要将人质移出外国
We're moving the hostages out of the country.
你的手怎么了?
What happened to your hand?
他们称之为哥伦比亚美甲
They call that a Colombian manicure.
这酷刑的绝妙之处在于
What's so great about it
它能让你感受最大程度的痛苦
is it's the maximum amount of pain,
但又不会死去
but you don't die.
所以现在你决定成为那个拿着钳子的人
So now you've decided to be the one holding the pliers.
每个人都会崩溃
Everybody breaks.
每个人
Everyone.
你丈夫
Your husband...
将会跪在我面前
is gonna kneel down in front of me...
并求我饶了你们的命
and beg for your lives.
然后你就会看着我杀掉他
And then you're gonna watch me kill him.
你不了解我丈夫
You don't know my husband.
我们没正式认识过 但是
Well, not officially, but...
我期待再次和他见面
I look forward to seeing him again.
坏孩子
Bad boys Bad boys
唱嘛 迈克
Come on, Mike.
坏孩子
Bad boys Bad boys
你打算怎么做
Whatchu you gonna do
对
Yeah.
敌人朝你袭来时 你打算怎么做
What you gonna do When they come for you
这就够了
That's enough, dawg. That's enough.
我们回头再继续唱
Okay, well, we'll circle back on that one.
好 飞机准备好了 20分钟后开始行动
All right. The plane is ready. We roll in 20.
这是一座废弃的游乐园 应该没有平民
It's an abandoned amusement park. There should be no civilians.
飞机将从南边降落 在一侧
Plane is gonna land from the south. On the one side.
马克斯和我将在飞机上
Marcus and I will be on the plane.
阿曼多会在水中奋力前行 两侧
Armando's gonna make his way in the water. The two side.
卡丽 丽塔 这条路是一进一出
Kelly, Rita. This road is one way in, one way out.
你守着那条路
You're holding that road.
东恩 你控制空中
Dorn, you're gonna control the air.
无人机在空中 干扰已激活 通讯安全
Drones in the air, jamming is active, comms are secure.
他们会以为洛克伍德正乘着飞机
As far as they know, Lockwood is on his way with the plane
将人质转移到古巴
to move the hostages to Cuba.
当他们带着人质靠近飞机时 就会很快被杀死
The second they get close to the plane with the hostages, it's quick kills.
消除所有威胁
Neutralise all threats.
这些混蛋杀了很多好警察
These motherfuckers killed a lot of good cops.
他们绑架了我的妻子和凯莉
They have my wife, they have Callie.
他们袭击了我们的家人
They attacked our families.
今天我们不能输
We not losing today.
嘿
Hey.
飞机一降落 只要你搞小动作
We get on the ground, you even flinch,
就会在0点24秒里死去
you'll be dead in .24 seconds.
我同意
I concur.
我在外面的平台上有一人把风
I got one lookout on the platform outside.
二号楼的屋顶上有一名狙击手
I got one sniper on the roof of building two.
让我看看
Tee those up.
大家继续前进
Everybody keep moving.
那些是什么?鳄鱼
What are those? Gators.
我以为这是一个废弃的 鳄鱼公园
I thought it was an abandoned gator park.
被人类遗弃
Abandoned by humans.
其实这是一个古老的游乐园
It's actually an old amusement park.
它占地10英亩 2017 年飓风"艾尔玛"之后被废弃
It sat on 10 acres, abandoned in 2017 after Hurricane Irma.
他们的主要景点是一只名叫杜克的白化鳄鱼
Their main attraction was an albino alligator named Duke...
他长16英尺 重900磅
...who was 16 feet long, 900 pounds.
"传说它还在那里"
"And legend has it he's still there."
完了
Fuck that.
阿曼多已经在他的位置
Armando's at his QTH.
人质现在出来了
Hostages are coming out now.
除麦格拉思外还有三人
McGrath plus three.
大家保持冷静
Everybody stay calm.
迈克
Mike.
迈克 能击中吗?
Mike, do you have the shot?
不行 我无法开枪
Negative. I do not have a shot. I do not have a shot.
迈克 他就在那边 我无法开枪
Mike, he's right there. I don't have it. I don't have it.
他们停下来了 为什么停下来?
They stopped. Why'd they stop?
糟糕
Shit.
我们走
Let's go.
阿曼多 他们正在靠近你
Armando, they're closing in on you.
他们看到他了?我不知道
Do they see him? I don't know.
迈克 马上 现在就是你的机会
Mike, now. Your chance is now.
他们能看见他 他们知道我们在这里
They can see him. They know we're here.
我无法开枪 不行
I don't have it. Negative. Negative. Negative.
你一定要开枪
You gotta take the fuckin' shot.
阿曼多暴露了
Armando's burnt.
该死 全面作战 开始行动
Shit. Full green. Engage.
卡丽 带我们去那里 快!
Kelly, get us there. Go, go, go!
敌人 码头西侧
Contact, west dock side.
东恩!干掉那个狙击手!
Dorn! Take out that sniper!
派出无人机
Sending the drone.
搞定
Got him.
现在不行 迈克!
Not now, Mike!
现在不行!
Not now!
没关系
It's okay.
不是你的错
Not your fault.
做个男人 大胆点吧 迈克
Cut that bitch-ass shit out, Mike.
我要可恶的迈克
I need Nasty Mike.
可恶的迈克!
Nasty Mike!
坏事发生了 但这并不意味着你很糟糕
Bad shit happens, but that doesn't mean you're bad.
做一头固执的驴好吗?这就对了
Do that donkey shit, a'ight? That's what I'm talking about.
就那样 就像那样
That shit right there. That's that shit right there.
坏孩子 坏孩子迈克 知道吗?
Bad boy. Bad boy. Bad Boy Mike. All right?
你是邻里的大灰狼
You're the big bad wolf in the neighbourhood
不坏意味着坏 但坏就意味着好
Not bad meaning bad but bad meaning good
东恩 消灭四边的车辆 收到
Dorn, take out the vehicles on the four side. Copy.
走!快走!
Go, go! Move it!
长官!我们被袭击 我们失去了卡车和外面三个人
Sir! We're taking heavies. We lost the trucks and three guys outside.
该死的!
Goddamn it!
设置两侧射击位置 让他们进来
Set firing positions, both sides. Let 'em in.
去
Go.
法警霍华德 弹药车现场的热信号显示发生爆炸
Marshal Howard, heat signature at the site of the AMMO van is showing explosions.
预计抵达时间15分钟
ETA 15 minutes.
东恩 我们需要掩护和内部情报 马上去
Dorn, we need cover and we need eyes inside. Go, now.
烟雾来了
Here comes the smoke.
我在后面掩护你
I got your six.
射杀那些混蛋!
Shoot those motherfuckers!
立即把无人机击毁!去!
Get those drones down now! Go!
快走!
Move, move, move!
上面!
Eyes up!
糟了!
Oh, shit!
这里就像乡巴佬侏罗纪公园
It's like redneck Jurassic Park in here.
我们马上离开这里
Let's get out of here, now.
卡丽 去
Kelly, go.
东恩 进去支援凯莉 我来追洛克伍德
Dorn, back up Kelly inside. I'm going after Lockwood.
宝贝 我来了
Babe, I'm comin'.
阿曼多 去救凯莉!
Armando, go for Callie!
放开!
Let go!
迈克!
Mike!
马克斯!
Marcus!
快走!
Go!
我没子弹了!
I'm out!
很高兴见到你 劳瑞先生
Nice to meet you, Mr Lowrey.
手榴弹!
Grenade!
噢 不
Oh sh--!
天啊!
Holy shit!
撑住!
Hang on!
停!
Stop!
克莉斯丁!
Christine!
混蛋
Shit.
糟糕
Oh sh--!
迈克 让我来!不!
Mike, I got this! No. No, no!
我来了 宝贝!
Here I come, baby! Here I come!
不!
No! No! No!
马克斯!
Marcus!
什么?你后面
What? Behind you.
天啊
Oh, shit.
我能搞定 迈克
I got this, Mike.
不过是小鳄鱼而已
It's just Dukey, baby.
我的枪 我的枪掉进水了 就在你的脚边
Marcus, my gun. I dropped my gun in the water. It's by your foot.
我不需要枪 迈克
I don't need no gun, Mike.
滚开吧 鳄鱼
Begone, gator.
你不该来这儿 小鳄鱼
This is not your place, Duke.
我谴责你!
I rebuke you!
看吧 迈克?
See, Mike?
这就是你命令宇宙的方式
That's how you command the universe.
枪呢?糟了!
Where's the gun? Where's the gun? Oh, shit!
快走
Go, go.
警告!请勿将手置于鳄鱼坑内
那混蛋种族主义 迈克
That motherfucker racist, Mike. That motherfucker racist!
迈克派我来
Mike sent me.
你一定要相信我
I need you to trust me.
快跑
Run.
跑!
Run!
加油 起身
Come on. Come on. Get up.
停!
Stop!
快去!我会拖慢你的速度
Go! I'll slow you down.
看到目的地
Eyes on location.
见鬼
Oh, shit.
你活着吗?
You alive?
混蛋
Shit.
好 嘿
Okay. Hey.
丽塔 停手 你不会向我开枪
Rita, stop this. You don't want to shoot me.
你说得对
You're right.
过来 好 没问题
Come here. Okay. Okay. It's okay.
我最讨厌政客
I fuckin' hate politicians.
快走!走!
Let's move! Go, go!
散开 带他们到楼上
Fan out. Take the team upstairs.
目标不在
No targets.
去上面!
Go topside!
好 这里
Okay. Okay, here.
放我下来 没事的
Put me down. It's okay. Okay.
你还好吗?还好
You okay? Yeah. Yeah.
嘿
Hey.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我来过这里
I've been here before.
糟了
Oh, shit.
你怎么让他抓住你了?
How did you let him catch you?
他真是太狡猾了 迈克
He's sneaky as hell, Mike.
我和你妻子正在争论
Your wife and I were having a debate.
看来她对你的印象有些夸大了
She seems to have an inflated impression of you.
迈克 嘿 宝贝
Mike. Hey, bae.
尽管如此 这已经是尽头了
Nevertheless, this is the end of the road.
他们其中一人就快死了
One of them is about to die.
你来选
You choose.
你不知道的是 麦格拉斯先生
What you don't know, Mr McGrath...
他们其中一人死不了
is one of 'em can't die.
你在说谁呢?
Who you talking 'bout?
一位智者告诉我 我将不得不做出艰难的选择
A wise man told me I was gonna have to make a hard choice.
在你选择之前 该要先和那个混蛋确认一下
You need to check with that motherfucker before you out here choosing shit.
你有五秒钟的时间 劳瑞先生
You have five seconds, Mr Lowrey.
我们需要更多时间 先生
We gonna need some more time, sir.
四 三
Four... three...
迈克 别做傻事
Mike. Don't you do no dumb shit.
二
...two...
迈克 嘿 我在这里
Mike. Mike. Hey. Hey. I'm here.
混蛋向我开枪了
Motherfucker done shot me.
该死的
Aw, damn.
来 让我看看 不 迈克 你这王八蛋又朝我开枪了
Here. Let me check it. Let me see. No, Mike. Your donkey ass shot me again.
让我看 别用你的手动我 迈克
Let me look at it. Don't touch me with your donkey hooves, Mike.
该死的
Damn, man.
听好 我被逼开枪
Listen. I had to fucking take the shot.
不 迈克 不
No, Mike. No.
马克斯 让我看看
Marcus. Let me take a look.
你看到了吗 克莉斯丁?
You see that shit, Christine?
我朝背心开枪 别再胡闹了 这个不重要好吗?
I shot you in your vest. Stop bitchin'. It don't matter. Okay?
你知道你把一生奉献给了什么 克莉斯丁?
You see what you done devoted your life to, Christine?
我已经看到阿瑞塔斯 正在接近
I've got eyes on Aretas. Moving in.
糟了 那是朱迪
Shit. That's Judy.
阿曼多 你听到吗?
Armando, do you copy?
糟了
Oh, shit.
妈妈 妈妈 不要
Mom. Mom, don't.
离她远点
Get away from her.
妈妈 马上!
Mom. Now!
妈妈 听我说 你不明白
Mom, listen to me, you don't understand.
凯莉 我要你听我的
Callie, I need you to listen to me.
我要你慢慢向右迈一步 向我走来
I want you to step slowly to your right and walk towards me.
妈妈 妈妈 我没事 好吗?
Mom. Mom, I'm fine, okay?
凯莉 我要你走开
Callie, I need you to move out of the way.
妈妈
Mom.
妈妈 别开枪!妈妈 他救了我 停!
Mom, don't shoot, don't shoot! Mom, he saved me. Stop!
朱迪!
Judy! Judy!
退后 迈克!把枪放下
Back off, Mike! Put the gun down.
他救了我的命
He saved my life.
求求你 妈妈
Please, Mom.
妈妈
Mom. Mom.
你中枪了吗?
Are you hit? Are you hit?
我没事
I'm good.
你没事?
You good?
你做得很好
You did good. You did good.
霍华德 你在哪里?
Howard. Where are you?
霍华德 你听到吗?
Howard. Do you copy?
霍华德 你在哪里?
Howard, what's your location?
走吧
Go.
在我改变主意之前
Before I change my mind.
我们走
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
嘿 你还好吗?
Hey. You good? You good?
嘿
Hey.
拿去
Take this.
往南去 别回头
Head south. Don't look back.
嘿
Hey.
我知道了
I got it.
乖一点
Be good.
你说了不算 警探
It's not up to you, detective.
快点 这里有受伤的警察
Come on, come on. We got injured cops here.
我需要你马上把令状给我
I need you to bring the writ to me now.
我知道
I know, I know, I know.
他怎么样了?他会挺过去的
How is he? You know, he'll pull through.
别吻他 克莉斯丁
Don't kiss him, Christine.
迈克 下辈子 你就做我的一双鞋
Mike, in our next life, you coming back as a pair of my shoes.
而且我不会穿袜子
And I ain't gonna wear no socks.
还会踩着各种大便
And I'mma step in all kind of shit.
迈阿密检察官和市长候选人亚当洛克伍德 和前陆军游骑兵詹姆斯麦格拉思
Miami DA and mayoral candidate Adam Lockwood and former Army Ranger James McGrath
今天早上在交火中丧生
were killed this morning in a firefight.
据信洛克伍德和麦格拉思
It is believed that Lockwood and McGrath were the key links
是迈阿密执法部门和贩毒集团之间的关键
between Miami law enforcement and cartels.
已故康拉德霍华德警监已完全无罪
The late Captain Howard has been fully exonerated.
联邦调查局和迈阿密警察局目前正在围捕同谋
Co-conspirators are currently being rounded up by the FBI and the Miami PD.
对被定罪的杀手阿曼多阿雷塔斯的搜寻仍在继续
The search for convicted killer Armando Aretas continues.
逃犯仍然逍遥法外
The fugitive remains at large.
嘿 我的家人们
Hey, hey, hey. My people.
特蕾莎在哪儿?她和小马克斯在秋千旁
Where's Theresa? She's with Little Marcus by the swings.
嘿 我刚要煮给你们吃
Hey. I'm about you hook you all up.
刚要煮给你们吃 请 我们很饿了
I'm about you hook you up. Please. We're starving.
看这个
Watch this.
搭档
Partner.
你这是要干什么?
What's all this?
你为什么要系围裙?
Why you got on an apron?
锻炼我的烧烤技巧
Work on my grill skills.
不 迈克 你要努力争取烤架
No, Mike, you gotta earn the grill.
这需要调味料和温度 你不能直接在我的烤架上做饭
This takes seasonings and temperatures. You can't just be cooking on my grill.
你的烤架?好笑了 这是一个公共公园
Your grill? Joker, this is a public park.
你看到的烤架并不是你的
You don't own every grill you see.
不如你去做点马铃薯沙拉 摆好桌子
You know what, Mike? Why don't you go make some potato salad and set the table.
休想派我去做杂活
Oh, you talking dirty.
这样吧 我不知道你脑子想的
Now, look. I don't... I don't know what you got going on
烧烤独裁是怎么回事 但你小看我了
with your barbecue dictatorship in your mind, but I ain't the one.
不管你喜不喜欢 我要在这个烤架上做饭
I'm cooking on this grill whether you like it or not.
迈克 抱歉 长官们
Hey, Mike-Excuse me, sirs.
你在干什么 雷吉?
What are you... What you doin', Reggie?
请求允许我煮鸡肉
Request permission to cook my chicken.
许可被拒绝 雷吉 去找其他地方吧 伙计
Permission denied, Reggie. Go ahead somewhere, man.
脱掉你的工作服 去和孩子们一起玩
Take your smock off and go play with the kids.
听着 这是烧烤的男士区
Listen, this is the man area of the barbecue.
恕我直言 我们很感激你拯救了我们所爱的人
Look, you know what? All due respect, we appreciate that you did save people that we love.
我们很感激 好吗?是的
We appreciate that, right? Yeah, we appreciate that.
我们真心感激 雷吉 好了
We appreciate that from here, Reggie. Yeah.
你走开 没错
Now, back the fuck up. Yeah.
好 这样吧 我愿意妥协
All right, look. I'm willing to compromise with you.
你可以用那一半的烤架 它很小 这一半我来用
You can work that half of the grill. It's small. And I'll work this half.
他还站在那里吗?
Is he still standing there?
没错
Yes, he is.
好奇怪
Huh, that's weird.
是的
Yeah.
现在他觉得他很强大
He think he hard now.
你该让那混蛋知道 他今天不能在这里煮鸡肉
You need to let that motherfucker know he ain't cooking no chicken out here today.
迈克 他在屋内杀了15个人
Mike. He killed 15 people at the house.
所以这事你管不了
So, you not gonna handle this shit.
好 我会让那混蛋煮鸡肉
Yeah, I'm gonna let that motherfucker cook the chicken.
他眼中有些奇怪的东西 我去做马铃薯沙拉
Yeah, there's something weird in his eyes. So I'mma make the potato salad.
我来摆好桌子 好
I'mma set the table. Yeah.
请求允许了 雷吉 你去吧
Permission granted, Reggie. There you go.
绝地战警: 生死与共
字幕翻译:析雯
公元前305年
快点 继续走啊
Come on. Bring your ass on.
天气太热了 没心情陪你耍性子
It's too hot out here for this shit.
如果我有一匹马就好了 至少马可以骑
Wish I had a horse. At least I could ride that motherfucker.
外面这么多新鲜空气 我却只能闻到你的臭味
All this free air out here, and I still smell your stinkin' ass.
我诅咒你 驴子
I curse you, donkey.
我要诅咒你生生世世
I curse you for all lifetimes.
你这该死的
You mother--
去你的吧 马克斯
Fuck you, Marcus.